Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪I plant miles of peach blossoms just for her♪
أزرع أميالاً من أزهار الخوخ خصيصاً من أجلها
♪Sweet words bloom upon those branches♪
♪تزهر الكلمات العذبة على تلك الأغصان♪
♪Love runs deep, trapped in longing♪
♪الحب عميق، محاصر في الشوق♪
♪Night listens answers to longing are the most terrifying♪
♪تستمع الليل إلى إجابات الشوق، وهي الأكثر رعباً♪
♪At my fingertips, worries drift and linger♪
♪على أطراف أصابعي، تتلاشى الهموم وتستمر♪
♪Having tasted a moment of carefree joy♪
♪ بعد أن تذوقت لحظة من الفرح الخالي من الهموم ♪
♪Today, I pluck romance and moonlight♪
اليوم، أقطف الرومانسية وضوء القمر
♪And weave them all into a painting♪
♪ واجمعها كلها في لوحة ♪
=The Ultimate Vow, Unknown to You=
=العهد الأسمى، الذي تجهله=
=Episode 13=
=الحلقة 13=
(A Celestial Realm of Joy)
(عالم سماوي من البهجة)
We have a few skilled performers today.
لدينا اليوم عدد قليل من الفنانين المهرة.
Please enjoy yourselves.
أتمنى لكم قضاء أوقات ممتعة.
Young Lady Shen, bear with it for now.
يا آنسة شين، تحملي الأمر قليلاً.
You'll need to smile beautifully later.
ستحتاجين إلى الابتسامة الجميلة لاحقاً.
Your Ladyship,
سيدتي،
everything is ready.
كل شيء جاهز.
The final show
العرض الختامي
is about to begin.
على وشك أن يبدأ.
Isn't that
أليس كذلك؟
Madam Su?
سيدتي سو؟
A boat courtesan's daughter.
ابنة عاهرة على متن قارب.
She's indeed inherited her mother's lowly fate.
لقد ورثت بالفعل مصير والدتها البائس.
True, though.
صحيح.
She's probably trying to return
ربما تحاول العودة
to where she truly belongs.
إلى حيث تنتمي حقاً.
Wasn't your mother
ألم تكن والدتك
climbing her way up
وهي تشق طريقها إلى الأعلى
with her face
بوجهها
and her body?
وجسدها؟
Your Ladyship, you seem to know my mother's past very well.
سيدتي، يبدو أنكِ على دراية جيدة بماضي والدتي.
Did you investigate for a long time?
هل أجريت تحقيقاً مطولاً؟
For today's show,
في حلقة اليوم،
you planned all this long ago.
لقد خططت لكل هذا منذ زمن بعيد.
The drug is ready.
الدواء جاهز.
The stage is set.
تم تجهيز المسرح.
All that's left is to put me on display.
لم يتبق سوى عرضي.
Do you all know
هل تعلمون جميعاً؟
why the Princess
لماذا الأميرة
brought me onto this stage tonight?
هل أوصلني هذا إلى هذه المنصة الليلة؟
I knew you'd use this trick.
كنت أعرف أنك ستستخدم هذه الحيلة.
That's why
لهذا السبب
I've been waiting here.
لقد كنت أنتظر هنا.
The Breath-Holding Technique lies in calming the mind.
تكمن تقنية حبس النفس في تهدئة العقل.
Feel the flow of breath in your body.
اشعر بتدفق التنفس في جسدك.
Yes.
نعم.
Like that.
هكذا.
But my heart
لكن قلبي
won't calm down.
لن يهدأ.
That's because you keep looking at me.
ذلك لأنك تستمر في النظر إليّ.
Concentrate.
يركز.
I...
أنا...
Remember this. No matter what danger you face in the future,
تذكر هذا. مهما كان الخطر الذي ستواجهه في المستقبل،
this technique can save your life.
هذه التقنية قد تنقذ حياتك.
Practice it well.
مارسها جيداً.
Focus.
ركز.
Tomorrow,
غداً،
I'll give you a fine show.
سأقدم لكم عرضاً رائعاً.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
Today,
اليوم،
I'll show everyone
سأري الجميع
what
ماذا
true dancing is.
الرقص الحقيقي هو...
(A Celestial Realm of Joy)
(عالم سماوي من البهجة)
Good!
جيد!
I've never seen such graceful dance.
لم أرَ رقصاً بهذه الرشاقة من قبل.
There's no trace of vulgarity at all.
لا يوجد أي أثر للابتذال على الإطلاق.
She looks like an immortal from the heavens.
تبدو وكأنها كائن خالد من السماء.
(A Celestial Realm of Joy)
(عالم سماوي من البهجة)
Good!
جيد!
Excellent!
ممتاز!
My mother taught me
علمتني أمي
to conduct myself with dignity
أن أتصرف بكرامة
and to dance with sincerity.
وأن يرقص بصدق.
Even as a boat courtesan,
حتى كعاهرة على متن قارب،
one must live with integrity.
يجب على المرء أن يعيش بنزاهة.
She may be a boat courtesan,
ربما تكون عاهرة على متن قارب،
but she lived honestly through her own skill.
لكنها عاشت بصدق بفضل مهارتها الخاصة.
That's better than some people
هذا أفضل من بعض الناس
who are born noble
الذين ولدوا نبلاء
but act despicably.
لكن يتصرفون بشكل دنيء.
You!
أنت!
Good!
جيد!
You wench!
يا لكِ من فتاة حقيرة!
Stop putting on airs.
توقف عن التظاهر.
Since you look down on my dancing,
بما أنك تنظر بازدراء إلى رقصي،
why not dance yourself?
لماذا لا ترقص أنت أيضاً؟
Who do you think you are
من تظن نفسك؟
to order me around?
هل تريد أن تأمرني؟
If you think
إذا كنت تعتقد
her skills are lacking,
مهاراتها غير كافية،
you must be exceptional yourself.
يجب أن تكون أنت نفسك متميزاً.
Why not have a fair contest
لماذا لا نجري مسابقة عادلة؟
in front of everyone here?
أمام الجميع هنا؟
This dance costume you're wearing
زي الرقص هذا الذي ترتدينه
looks rather familiar.
يبدو مألوفاً نوعاً ما.
How brazen of you.
يا لك من وقح!
You're actually wearing the phoenix robe of a crown princess.
أنتِ في الواقع ترتدين رداء العنقاء الخاص بأميرة ولية العهد.
Have you gone mad dreaming of becoming a crown princess?
هل جننتِ من كثرة أحلامكِ بأن تصبحي ولية العهد؟
You wench!
يا لكِ من فتاة حقيرة!
How dare you frame me!
كيف تجرؤ على تلفيق التهمة لي!
There's no need for me to say more, right?
لا داعي لأن أقول المزيد، أليس كذلك؟
Qingru.
كينغرو.
There's no need to trouble yourself, Your Highness.
لا داعي لإزعاج نفسك يا صاحب السمو.
I'm just a boat courtesan's daughter
أنا مجرد ابنة عاهرة على متن قارب
who isn't worthy of your concern.
من لا يستحق اهتمامك.
(Chengguang Hall)
(قاعة تشنغ قوانغ)
General Su's body hasn't been found yet.
لم يتم العثور على جثة الجنرال سو حتى الآن.
I afraid the dungeon...
أخشى الزنزانة...
No one should know about this.
لا ينبغي لأحد أن يعلم بهذا الأمر.
Yes.
نعم.
Come out.
يخرج.
Where did you lock him up?
أين حبسته؟
Even if he's still alive,
حتى لو كان لا يزال على قيد الحياة،
what can you do?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل؟
You still
ما زلتَ
can't let him go?
لا يمكنك تركه يرحل؟
Let go.
اتركه.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
You're insane.
أنت مجنون.
Let go.
اتركه.
♪I plant miles of peach blossoms just for her♪
أزرع أميالاً من أزهار الخوخ خصيصاً من أجلها
♪Sweet words bloom upon those branches♪
♪تزهر الكلمات العذبة على تلك الأغصان♪
♪Love runs deep, trapped in longing♪
♪الحب عميق، محاصر في الشوق♪
When we're here,
عندما نكون هنا،
you'll still love me.
ستظل تحبني.
♪Having tasted a moment of carefree joy♪
♪ بعد أن تذوقت لحظة من الفرح الخالي من الهموم ♪
We'll be just like before.
سنعود كما كنا من قبل.
♪Today, I pluck romance and moonlight♪
اليوم، أقطف الرومانسية وضوء القمر
No one will disturb us.
لن يزعجنا أحد.
Never.
أبداً.
♪And weave them all into a painting♪
♪ واجمعها كلها في لوحة ♪
Your Highness, I'm here to tend to your wounds.
يا صاحب السمو، أنا هنا لأعتني بجراحك.
I heard Young Lady Shen went to bathe earlier.
سمعت أن الشابة شين ذهبت للاستحمام في وقت سابق.
Your Highness, could it be
صاحب السمو، هل يمكن أن يكون
that your injury...
أن إصابتك...
Young Lady Shen is strong-willed.
الشابة شين تتمتع بإرادة قوية.
She probably won't treat you sincerely.
ربما لن تعاملك بصدق.
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Since you care so much for His Highness,
بما أنك تهتم كثيراً بصاحب السمو،
why don't you take care of him?
لماذا لا تعتني به؟
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
You wench!
يا لكِ من فتاة حقيرة!
Get out.
اخرج.
What did I do wrong?
ما الخطأ الذي ارتكبته؟
She's just a lowly woman!
إنها مجرد امرأة وضيعة!
I said get out.
قلتُ: اخرج.
What am I lacking compared to her?
ما الذي ينقصني مقارنة بها؟
I'm a Princess.
أنا أميرة.
- She's nothing but a lowly... - Shut up!
- إنها ليست سوى حثالة... - اصمت!
You don't deserve to speak of her.
أنت لا تستحق أن تتحدث عنها.
Get out.
اخرج.
Bring me some aphrodisiac powder.
أحضر لي بعض المسحوق المنشط جنسياً.
Your Ladyship, but
سيدتي، ولكن
this goes against the rules.
هذا يخالف القواعد.
Rules?
قواعد؟
This fine mutton-fat jade bracelet
هذا السوار المصنوع من اليشم الفاخر المصنوع من دهن الضأن
matters more than any rules.
أهم من أي قواعد.
Your Ladyship,
سيدتي،
this Longbi Incense is very strong.
هذا البخور من نوع لونغبي قوي جداً.
Be careful when using it.
كن حذراً عند استخدامه.
Thank you for your reminder, imperial physician.
شكراً لك على تذكيرك، أيها الطبيب الإمبراطوري.
(Chengguang Hall)
(قاعة تشنغ قوانغ)
(Your Highness,)
(صاحب السمو،)
(since you're so heartless,)
(لأنك عديم الرحمة للغاية،)
(don't blame me for being ruthless.)
(لا تلوموني على قسوتي.)
This liquor.
هذا المشروب الكحولي.
Something's with this liquor.
هناك شيء ما مريب في هذا المشروب.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
let me take care of you.
دعني أعتني بك.
Shen Qingru,
شين تشينغرو,
didn't you want to see His Highness?
ألم ترغب برؤية صاحب السمو؟
Tonight, I especially brought him to you.
الليلة، أحضرته إليكِ خصيصاً.
What did you do to him?
ماذا فعلت به؟
Me?
أنا؟
What could I possibly do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
I merely let His Highness taste
لقد سمحتُ لصاحب السمو فقط بتذوق الطعام.
the bitterness of love.
مرارة الحب.